http://store.workshopsupply.com/catalogue/privacy.php?osCsid=a185a0947e9b4dbf3805af2c81a269e9

Sign In Create an Account
0 items
Search our Site...
Go
Sign up for your FREE eNewsletter!
Pocket Hole
Rotary...
Router...
Safety
Sharpening
Table Saw...
Tool Maintenance
Turning Tools
Gift Certificates
PLANSBOOKS
BONUS !
PRIVACY
Workshop Supply respects and protects your privacy.
To protect your personal information, we have safeguards that comply with the Federal Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act.
Any information you provide to Workshop Supply when purchasing, requesting information, quotes or subscribing for Workshop Supply's products and services is maintained and accessible only by Workshop Supply. We keep your information for our own records only. We DO NOT sell or otherwise distribute our mailing list.
We limit access to personal information to Workshop Supply employees who need to access this information. Your name and address is used for shipping your order, catalogues or other related information. Your phone number will be used if there is a problem with your order, or if we need to contact you. We may occasionally call our customers to see how our service is measuring up, but we do not do "telemarketing" by phone or fax.
Your email address is used to confirm your purchases, respond to your inquiries or requests. We also use your email address for sending our latest e-newsletter.
Credit card numbers are never kept on file. The numbers are deleted as soon as the transaction has been approved.
You will find links to other web sites at www.workshopsupply.com. Workshop Supply is not responsible for the practices and/or content of these web sites. Please view their Privacy Policies before submitting your personal information.
Workshop Supply will never willfully disclose individually identifiable information about our customers to any third party without first receiving our customer's permission.
INTERNET SECURITY
Workshop Supply believes that strong electronic privacy & security is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium.
All information in regards to an order is encrypted using the latest encryption protocols and is processed on a secure server, even if you add items to the shopping cart in order to print out a form to mail with your payment to our office, that transaction takes place on a secure server. Credit card numbers are never kept on file after the transaction has been approved.
Workshop Supply will not disclose any information about any individual user, client or customer except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.
UNSOLICITED EMAIL
Workshop Supply does not use or support the use of unsolicited email. Any affiliate using junk lists (unsolicited or "nonopt-in" email lists) will not be paid and their affiliate account will be cancelled immediately.
RETURNS
Absolutely 100% guarantee - If for any reason you are not 100% satisfied, even if you ordered the wrong size, we want you to be another satisfied customer!   "No Questions Asked" (unused) returns are accepted for 90 days from invoice date.
No returns without prior consent. Please call 1-800-387-5716 for a return authorization number.
CONTACT US
Do you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy? Please contact us by email: info @ workshopsupply . com (no spaces) or by postal mail ( PO Box 160, Embro, Ontario N0J 1J0 ).
Continue
Get your free woodworking eNewsletter...
Click here to sign up now!SAVE $$$ EVERY WEEK!
Your info is safe - we do not share. You can unsubscribe at any time.
